I'll give it to you straight.
Sometimes my feedback has been called
chemotherapy
because it takes you as close as you can
to dying, but it's there to save you.
And remember,
although sometimes I am a ruthless,
horrible twat,
in my eyes,
the worst thing I could ever say to
someone is, "Yeah, mate, content
looks good, mate.
Crack on." That's the worst thing I could
say.
[upbeat music]
I'm all about people reacting to other
reels,
but the one thing I will say here is
sometimes you need to preface what it
is you're reacting to.
So for instance,
you could just come front and center
and go, "You're not going to
believe this." Then you get into this.
Just something that shows me
that there's a react coming because I feel
like I'm
watching the original.
[upbeat music]
Captain out.
Okay.
I like this idea of what you're doing
here.
A little bit slow to get into.
So far we're what?
Six, seven seconds in, no context.
Altitude's a little low.
Could you give me the controls
and I'll go higher?
Don't worry about that, mate. No, no.
Just think too many people have left.
Here we make our own happiness, yeah?
We've always got to optimize our content
for a cold audience.
We've always got to think about people not
knowing us, not liking us.
So we have to be very mindful of their
time